-- 2025 / 12 / 17 --
# Time is Money | Patch : 0.0.0 |
Simple idle game about converting time into money.


## Installation
Pending, it is possible to run the project simply by taking the primary folder
and dragging it over the love.exe. (Requires love to be installed, of course.)


## Credits & License 
Written in Lua using the Löve2d engine. (https://love2d.org/wiki/love)

Disclaimer, License is pending.